<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Soirée, a night of fabulous music</title>
    <link href="https://gapsoiree.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://gapsoiree.com" />
    <updated>2021-08-20T00:45:58+10:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Music Supporters Group</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://gapsoiree.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Three Weeks To Go</title>
        <author>
            <name>Music Supporters Group</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gapsoiree.com/three-weeks-to-go/"/>
        <id>https://gapsoiree.com/three-weeks-to-go/</id>

        <updated>2021-08-20T00:45:58+10:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It is now only three more weeks until the Soirée, a night of fabulous music in The Gap with fantastic groups of local musicians performing on Saturday 11th September. Tickets are now available, so make sure to book soon to get the seats of your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It is now only three more weeks until the Soirée, a night of fabulous music in The Gap with fantastic groups of local musicians performing on Saturday 11th September. Tickets are <a href="https://gapsoiree.com/tickets/">now available</a>, so make sure to book soon to get the seats of your choice.</p>
<p>Queenslanders really came together in the last few weeks to help keep community spread from the recent COVID outbreaks down to a minimum, and the results have spoken for themselves. Restrictions are now beginning to ease, so we are still confident that the Soirée will not be impacted. We were already following Qld Health's advice on being COVID Safe, and continue to monitor the latest advice. The ticketing is for allocated seating to keep in line with this advice, and we have also enabled a feature that the ticketing service provides of automatically blocking a seat between separate bookings. This will help to maintain social distancing between groups of attendees while seated. It won't allow us to get to 100% capacity (that would be a nice problem to have), but will help to keep some people more comfortable about being in an indoor venue at this time.</p>
<p>Masks will still likely be mandatory while indoors, and if that is the case we will be requiring the use of masks while in the venue. Even if these restrictions are relaxed before then, we would still encourage the use of masks.</p>
<p>So come out on Saturday 11th September to celebrate local music and catch up with friends, family and neighbours.</p>
<p>See you at the Soirée!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Soirée Tickets Now Available</title>
        <author>
            <name>Music Supporters Group</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gapsoiree.com/tickets-now-available/"/>
        <id>https://gapsoiree.com/tickets-now-available/</id>

        <updated>2021-07-08T08:00:00+10:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This is most exciting! Tickets for Soirée, a night of fabulous music, are now available! Tell your friends and family, get them along, and also share on your social media. Entry is $25 with a bar and light refreshments available. Doors open at 6pm, and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This is most exciting! Tickets for Soirée, a night of fabulous music, are <a href="https://gapsoiree.com/tickets/">now available</a>! Tell your friends and family, get them along, and also share on your social media.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-xs.jpg 300w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-sm.jpg 480w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-md.jpg 768w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/13/responsive/Soiree-2021-Tickets-On-Sale-Horizontal-2xl.jpg 1600w"  alt="" width="1200" height="630"></figure>
<p>Entry is $25 with a bar and light refreshments available. Doors open at 6pm, and the performance starts at 7pm. Seating is allocated, so get in early to select your preferred seats.</p>
<p>You can also read more about the wonderful and talented artists that we have performing on the night.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/slade-gibson-and-melissa-gill/">Slade Gibson and Melissa Gill</a></li>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/tessitura-acapella/">Tessitura Acapella</a></li>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/the-vocalise-duo/">The Vocalise Duo</a></li>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/brisbane-folk-quartet/">Brisbane Folk Quartet</a></li>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/mint/">MINT</a></li>
<li><a href="https://gapsoiree.com/duo-key/">Duo Key</a></li>
</ul>
<p>While you are waiting for the performances to begin, selected senior students from The Gap State School's instrumental music program will be playing in the foyer. During interval, the talented String Quartet from The Gap State High School will be performing for your listening pleasure.</p>
<p>This will be a COVID-safe event in compliance with Qld Health's guidelines. Check in with the <a href="https://www.covid19.qld.gov.au/check-in-qld" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Check In Qld app</a> will be required before entry to the venue. If you do not have the app available to you, our volunteers will be able to assist you.</p>
<p>Grab those tickets for you, your family and your friends, and we'll see you at the Soirée!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Official Launch</title>
        <author>
            <name>Music Supporters Group</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gapsoiree.com/official-launch/"/>
        <id>https://gapsoiree.com/official-launch/</id>

        <updated>2021-06-23T21:06:10+10:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We are pleased to announce the full line-up for the Soirée on 11 September 2021. We have a great range of artists ready to delight with different styles of music. More information about the artists will be revealed in the coming weeks on this website&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We are pleased to announce the full line-up for the Soirée on 11 September 2021.</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-xs.jpg 300w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-sm.jpg 480w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-md.jpg 768w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/10/responsive/Soiree-2021-Announcement-Horizontal-2xl.jpg 1600w"  alt="Soirée announcement post" width="1200" height="630"></figure>
<p>We have a great range of artists ready to delight with different styles of music.</p>
<ul>
<li>Slade Gibson and Melissa Gill</li>
<li>Tessitura Acapella</li>
<li>MINT</li>
<li>Duo Key</li>
<li>Brisbane Folk Quartet</li>
<li>The Vocalise Duo</li>
</ul>
<p>More information about the artists will be revealed in the coming weeks on this website and on our socials, so make sure to follow us on <a href="https://facebook.com/gapsoiree" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a> or <a href="https://twitter.com/gapsoiree" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> to keep up to date with all of the latest news.</p>
<p>Tickets will go on sale on July 8. It will be allocated seating, so get in quick to choose your preferred seats. Along with requiring attendees to scan in using the Check In Qld app, this also helps to maintain compliance with current COVID restrictions defined by QLD Health. These measures will help us all to stay safe and be able to enjoy more of these live music events featuring local artists from our beautiful city.</p>
<p>We are looking forward to seeing you at the Soirée in September!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Save the Date</title>
        <author>
            <name>Music Supporters Group</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gapsoiree.com/save-the-date/"/>
        <id>https://gapsoiree.com/save-the-date/</id>

        <updated>2021-06-23T19:51:49+10:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We are very proud to announce a date for the next Soirée, a night of fabulous music showcasing musical talent for the local and surrounding areas. The next Soirée will be on Saturday 11 September 2021 at The Gap State School MPB, starting at 7pm.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We are very proud to announce a date for the next <span style="font-weight: 400;">Soirée, a night of fabulous music showcasing musical talent for the local and surrounding areas.</span></p>
<figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-xs.jpg 300w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-sm.jpg 480w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-md.jpg 768w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://gapsoiree.com/media/posts/1/responsive/Soiree-2021-Save-the-date-Horizontal-2-2xl.jpg 1600w"  alt="" width="1920" height="1080"></figure>
<p>The next <span style="font-weight: 400;">Soirée will be on Saturday 11 September 2021 at The Gap State School MPB, starting at 7pm. We have six artists and groups lined up to perform a variety of musical styles and genres.</span></p>
<p>The <span style="font-weight: 400;">Soirée in 2019 was a restart of the long-running Soirée series presented by the Music Supporters Group, and was the first major event in the new Multi-Purpose Building at The Gap State School. This year's event will build on the successful 2019 event with more performances from local artists and groups. While we also now have COVID restrictions to deal with as well, we are planning for this year's event to be even bigger and better.</span></p>
<p>More announcements will be appearing soon, along with how and where to purchase tickets. Keep an eye on this website or follow our <a href="https://fb.me/gapsoiree" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/GapSoiree" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> pages to be informed of new announcements as they happen.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
